{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472488493","data":{"timestamp":" 947472488492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jani_jani-tope-hiki"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jani"," userResponse":" jani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472497115","data":{"timestamp":" 947472497115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuni_elsa-kuni-mbao"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuni"," userResponse":" kuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472505177","data":{"timestamp":" 947472505177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" nini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472517481","data":{"timestamp":" 947472517481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nani_mara-nani-tele"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472525918","data":{"timestamp":" 947472525918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pini_jitu-pini-isha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pini"," userResponse":" pini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472535124","data":{"timestamp":" 947472535124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_geni_geni-kumi-jike"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" geni"," userResponse":" geni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472545104","data":{"timestamp":" 947472545104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tani_tani-lala-vuta"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tani"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472553806","data":{"timestamp":" 947472553806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jani_yadi-jani-maua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jani"," userResponse":" jani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472563283","data":{"timestamp":" 947472563283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jani_neno-yetu-jani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jani"," userResponse":" jani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472571976","data":{"timestamp":" 947472571976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nani_pana-nani-lori"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472577765","data":{"timestamp":" 947472577764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 43c954f1-9f0f-4d36-a5e2-c49783a4bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nani_pana-nani-lori"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472600711","data":{"timestamp":" 947472600710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" MFUKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472608493","data":{"timestamp":" 947472608492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" MFUKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472610117","data":{"timestamp":" 947472610116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472614265","data":{"timestamp":" 947472614265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472615867","data":{"timestamp":" 947472615866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanzoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472622666","data":{"timestamp":" 947472622665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanzoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" START_MWANZONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472623889","data":{"timestamp":" 947472623888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanzoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472625525","data":{"timestamp":" 947472625524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472629158","data":{"timestamp":" 947472629158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472630761","data":{"timestamp":" 947472630760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" geni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GENI"," userResponse":" GENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472634290","data":{"timestamp":" 947472634290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" geni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GENI"," userResponse":" GENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472635886","data":{"timestamp":" 947472635885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472639764","data":{"timestamp":" 947472639764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472641350","data":{"timestamp":" 947472641350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472645482","data":{"timestamp":" 947472645482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472647065","data":{"timestamp":" 947472647064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472650203","data":{"timestamp":" 947472650202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472651826","data":{"timestamp":" 947472651825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gizani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZANI"," userResponse":" GIZANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472656985","data":{"timestamp":" 947472656985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gizani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GIZANI"," userResponse":" START_GIZANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472659109","data":{"timestamp":" 947472659109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gizani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZANI"," userResponse":" GIZANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472660709","data":{"timestamp":" 947472660708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOKENI"," userResponse":" TOKENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472665218","data":{"timestamp":" 947472665217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TOKENI"," userResponse":" START_TOKENI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472666876","data":{"timestamp":" 947472666875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOKENI"," userResponse":" TOKENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472668897","data":{"timestamp":" 947472668896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472669010","data":{"timestamp":" 947472669010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e3411ae8-9834-4849-a89f-a7b517e7afaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ni.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tokeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOKENI"," userResponse":" TOKENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472693183","data":{"timestamp":" 947472693182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWANI"," userResponse":" ZIWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472694264","data":{"timestamp":" 947472694263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWANI"," userResponse":" ZIWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472700347","data":{"timestamp":" 947472700346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yaani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAANI"," userResponse":" YAANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472701421","data":{"timestamp":" 947472701420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yaani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAANI"," userResponse":" YAANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472706703","data":{"timestamp":" 947472706703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chumbani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472707748","data":{"timestamp":" 947472707748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chumbani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472714060","data":{"timestamp":" 947472714060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" START_MFUKONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472715975","data":{"timestamp":" 947472715974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" START_MFUKONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472717937","data":{"timestamp":" 947472717937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472719018","data":{"timestamp":" 947472719017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfukoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKONI"," userResponse":" MFUKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472728642","data":{"timestamp":" 947472728642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sahani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472729709","data":{"timestamp":" 947472729708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sahani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472732760","data":{"timestamp":" 947472732760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muthoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" START_MUTHONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472735177","data":{"timestamp":" 947472735177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muthoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472736223","data":{"timestamp":" 947472736222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muthoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472744307","data":{"timestamp":" 947472744306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitandani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDANI"," userResponse":" START_KITANDANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472748178","data":{"timestamp":" 947472748177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitandani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDANI"," userResponse":" START_KITANDANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472749984","data":{"timestamp":" 947472749983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitandani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472751048","data":{"timestamp":" 947472751048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitandani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDANI"," userResponse":" KITANDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472757504","data":{"timestamp":" 947472757503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lakini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" START_LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472762766","data":{"timestamp":" 947472762766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lakini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472763835","data":{"timestamp":" 947472763834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lakini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472769128","data":{"timestamp":" 947472769127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PAANI"," userResponse":" START_PAANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472771780","data":{"timestamp":" 947472771779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PAANI"," userResponse":" START_PAANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472773267","data":{"timestamp":" 947472773266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472774338","data":{"timestamp":" 947472774337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAANI"," userResponse":" PAANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472777749","data":{"timestamp":" 947472777748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472778804","data":{"timestamp":" 947472778803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472782214","data":{"timestamp":" 947472782212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472782352","data":{"timestamp":" 947472782352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472808904","data":{"timestamp":" 947472808904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472822227","data":{"timestamp":" 947472822226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" e0bff912-c3cd-4837-a927-9382cb5a7b01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ni.rand.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472846687","data":{"timestamp":" 947472846686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472849685","data":{"timestamp":" 947472849684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472852113","data":{"timestamp":" 947472852112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472855342","data":{"timestamp":" 947472855341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472858626","data":{"timestamp":" 947472858625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" KOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472861658","data":{"timestamp":" 947472861657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472864873","data":{"timestamp":" 947472864872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kabisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472869137","data":{"timestamp":" 947472869136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elsa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELSA"," userResponse":" ELSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472872092","data":{"timestamp":" 947472872091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" MAKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472875203","data":{"timestamp":" 947472875202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472878694","data":{"timestamp":" 947472878692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472878822","data":{"timestamp":" 947472878821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 3b96d368-b582-451f-9d72-3f1ac1b83744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472909987","data":{"timestamp":" 947472909987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lisa_babu-lisa-hema"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lisa"," userResponse":" lisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472918615","data":{"timestamp":" 947472918615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kisa_kuja-huko-kisa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kisa"," userResponse":" kisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472927106","data":{"timestamp":" 947472927105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lisa_bibi-lisa-huko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lisa"," userResponse":" lisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472935794","data":{"timestamp":" 947472935793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rosa_zetu-rosa-ubao"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rosa"," userResponse":" rosa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472944022","data":{"timestamp":" 947472944021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rosa_rosa-ubao-kaka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rosa"," userResponse":" rosa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472952088","data":{"timestamp":" 947472952088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tisa_taji-tisa-haki"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tisa"," userResponse":" tisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472960901","data":{"timestamp":" 947472960901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tisa_goso-tisa-osha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tisa"," userResponse":" tisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472969384","data":{"timestamp":" 947472969384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tisa_kinu-huwa-tisa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tisa"," userResponse":" tisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472978083","data":{"timestamp":" 947472978083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_lake-hawa-hasa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472986668","data":{"timestamp":" 947472986667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sasa_pole-kipi-sasa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sasa"," userResponse":" sasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472992445","data":{"timestamp":" 947472992443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 6d38064d-2531-4ca3-b4f3-5acfac5e8b6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_sasa_pole-kipi-sasa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473016636","data":{"timestamp":" 947473016635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sasa_pesa_sasa_rosa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473023258","data":{"timestamp":" 947473023258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" lisa_pesa_palesa_lisa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473029895","data":{"timestamp":" 947473029895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palesa_pesa_nosisa_palesa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473036525","data":{"timestamp":" 947473036525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palesa_sasa_palesa_elsa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473043957","data":{"timestamp":" 947473043957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palesa_sasa_palesa_elsa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473050602","data":{"timestamp":" 947473050601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" elsa_elsa_rosa_sasa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473057230","data":{"timestamp":" 947473057230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palesa_palesa_kosa_rosa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473063887","data":{"timestamp":" 947473063886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_elsa_makosa_rosa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473070532","data":{"timestamp":" 947473070532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" pesa_sasa_rosa_pesa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473077164","data":{"timestamp":" 947473077163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" pesa_sasa_pesa_lisa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473083801","data":{"timestamp":" 947473083800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_makosa_pesa_nosisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.sa.show.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473095885","data":{"timestamp":" 947473095885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 510916be-35ce-4a29-8323-563b2e50e2b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.sa.show.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_makosa_pesa_nosisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473120379","data":{"timestamp":" 947473120378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisa_sisa-maji-kana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisa"," userResponse":" sisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473128887","data":{"timestamp":" 947473128887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kosa_muda-aina-kosa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kosa"," userResponse":" kosa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473137623","data":{"timestamp":" 947473137623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_elsa_elsa-kato-miye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" elsa"," userResponse":" elsa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473146327","data":{"timestamp":" 947473146326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_kapu-hasa-dada"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473154543","data":{"timestamp":" 947473154543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_hasa-nono-kuoa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473162871","data":{"timestamp":" 947473162871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sasa_pana-sasa-anga"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sasa"," userResponse":" sasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473171148","data":{"timestamp":" 947473171148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lisa_jike-lisa-humo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lisa"," userResponse":" lisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473179511","data":{"timestamp":" 947473179511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_naro-hasa-lima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473188437","data":{"timestamp":" 947473188437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sasa_giza-sare-sasa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sasa"," userResponse":" sasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473197016","data":{"timestamp":" 947473197016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kasa_kasa-yowe-watu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kasa"," userResponse":" kasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473202800","data":{"timestamp":" 947473202798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 4ed35343-e402-49ff-8443-9599c100919b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kasa_kasa-yowe-watu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473221739","data":{"timestamp":" 947473221737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473222813","data":{"timestamp":" 947473222813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473228230","data":{"timestamp":" 947473228229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473229298","data":{"timestamp":" 947473229298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473234670","data":{"timestamp":" 947473234670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" MAKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473235744","data":{"timestamp":" 947473235743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" MAKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473239068","data":{"timestamp":" 947473239067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473240134","data":{"timestamp":" 947473240133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473245060","data":{"timestamp":" 947473245059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISA"," userResponse":" LISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473246120","data":{"timestamp":" 947473246119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISA"," userResponse":" LISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473249796","data":{"timestamp":" 947473249795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473250862","data":{"timestamp":" 947473250862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473256375","data":{"timestamp":" 947473256375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473257444","data":{"timestamp":" 947473257443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473261707","data":{"timestamp":" 947473261706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" KOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473262786","data":{"timestamp":" 947473262785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" KOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473267274","data":{"timestamp":" 947473267273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISA"," userResponse":" KISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473268337","data":{"timestamp":" 947473268337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISA"," userResponse":" KISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473272962","data":{"timestamp":" 947473272961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473274012","data":{"timestamp":" 947473274011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473276899","data":{"timestamp":" 947473276896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473277019","data":{"timestamp":" 947473277019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 0b81ae73-b8df-4b20-9315-527da2fa9fc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473320886","data":{"timestamp":" 947473320886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473322988","data":{"timestamp":" 947473322988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473331934","data":{"timestamp":" 947473331934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473338596","data":{"timestamp":" 947473338596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473346901","data":{"timestamp":" 947473346901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473348758","data":{"timestamp":" 947473348758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473359808","data":{"timestamp":" 947473359808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473367110","data":{"timestamp":" 947473367110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473369872","data":{"timestamp":" 947473369872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473379616","data":{"timestamp":" 947473379616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473381926","data":{"timestamp":" 947473381926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473390808","data":{"timestamp":" 947473390808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473392357","data":{"timestamp":" 947473392357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473408618","data":{"timestamp":" 947473408618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473415527","data":{"timestamp":" 947473415527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473423875","data":{"timestamp":" 947473423875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473426105","data":{"timestamp":" 947473426105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473432274","data":{"timestamp":" 947473432274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473442538","data":{"timestamp":" 947473442538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473450621","data":{"timestamp":" 947473450621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473458295","data":{"timestamp":" 947473458294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473468321","data":{"timestamp":" 947473468321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473479348","data":{"timestamp":" 947473479348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473482103","data":{"timestamp":" 947473482103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473496455","data":{"timestamp":" 947473496455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473500372","data":{"timestamp":" 947473500372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473509110","data":{"timestamp":" 947473509110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473515712","data":{"timestamp":" 947473515712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473518455","data":{"timestamp":" 947473518455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473529538","data":{"timestamp":" 947473529538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473537038","data":{"timestamp":" 947473537038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473539209","data":{"timestamp":" 947473539209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473554530","data":{"timestamp":" 947473554528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" daf8db07-0f7c-4125-8a3e-85a3a849bbb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473602745","data":{"timestamp":" 947473602745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473609590","data":{"timestamp":" 947473609590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473612170","data":{"timestamp":" 947473612170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473634680","data":{"timestamp":" 947473634679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473636748","data":{"timestamp":" 947473636748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473645432","data":{"timestamp":" 947473645432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473651674","data":{"timestamp":" 947473651674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473654226","data":{"timestamp":" 947473654226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473664946","data":{"timestamp":" 947473664946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473667590","data":{"timestamp":" 947473667590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473676588","data":{"timestamp":" 947473676588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473678711","data":{"timestamp":" 947473678711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473687941","data":{"timestamp":" 947473687941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473690839","data":{"timestamp":" 947473690839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473706632","data":{"timestamp":" 947473706631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473712500","data":{"timestamp":" 947473712500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473719036","data":{"timestamp":" 947473719035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473729790","data":{"timestamp":" 947473729790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473732293","data":{"timestamp":" 947473732293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473741644","data":{"timestamp":" 947473741644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473743837","data":{"timestamp":" 947473743836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473753792","data":{"timestamp":" 947473753792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473779005","data":{"timestamp":" 947473779005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473787077","data":{"timestamp":" 947473787076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473789501","data":{"timestamp":" 947473789501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473804347","data":{"timestamp":" 947473804346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 9eec4ca4-1a45-4c76-8ee8-97037cad91c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473817229","data":{"timestamp":" 947473817229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473820536","data":{"timestamp":" 947473820536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" itakuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAKUWA"," userResponse":" ITAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473823639","data":{"timestamp":" 947473823639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473827110","data":{"timestamp":" 947473827110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473830031","data":{"timestamp":" 947473830031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lililokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473833908","data":{"timestamp":" 947473833907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473837184","data":{"timestamp":" 947473837183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" SAWASAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473840757","data":{"timestamp":" 947473840755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uliokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473844155","data":{"timestamp":" 947473844154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473847471","data":{"timestamp":" 947473847470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alijawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.wa.rand.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473851207","data":{"timestamp":" 947473851206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" alijawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473851327","data":{"timestamp":" 947473851327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_054748"," gameId":" 236f61c1-9295-4b1f-ab78-e021b06fb5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.wa.rand.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alijawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}